Our only fighters are you and Yuri!
Hey! Look at this, Quon.
Is that a music box?
Could I listen to it?
I demand perfection and completeness in every respect.
Please remember that, Rookie-kun.
My voice...
Both.
I want to save them all.
And that won't change in a thousand years.
What are you people?
We're attractors.
According to Kannazuki, we've awakened.
I want to save everyone, no matter what.
Others like you and Yuuma-kun, who don't know what to do...
Everyone.
Quon-sama?
I heard your heart moaning in pain.
Be careful.
You're defenceless in your sleep.
You're attracted to a strong will.
I understand.
But I can't do anything about it.
Don't worry.
I'll stay by your side until you sleep.
No, please don't worry about me.
Please.
Crime scene to HQ.
We've confirmed the death of a gun victim at 2550.
We'll bring the victim in a car and turn him in for autopsy.
This is HQ. Roger.
Did that sting?
A bit.
If it's really bad, do you want me to disconnect your nerves?
Please don't.
You'd be sending me into a world of darkness, where I couldn't move my limbs.
I was just being nice.
By the way, what are you reading?
In Search of Lost Time.
Ah, Proust.
I read that when I was young.
It's a very long novel.
You know, I don't get you.
You could just download it into your brain.
There's no need to convert it into visual information.
It's just an old habit.
I still don't understand. You can directly access any data.
I turned out to be incompatible.
But in return, I can access your raw data.
How are the rookies?
Epsilon's simulating the investigation.
Of the serial murder case?
Yeah.
He wasn't satisfied with the investigation team's report,
although that's just a fragment of the
discontent in his psychological control system.
Show me the most recent crime scene.
Roger.
The victim was stabbed once with a knife, causing his death.
After the victim died, the culprit straddled his back and stabbed him ten or so more times.
It's a typical random murder.
Figured anything out, Novice Detective-san?
One advantage of being a cyborg is that I don't gain weight from eating popsicles.
The cause of death was a bullet that fractured his cervical vertebrae.
No sign of drugs or any particular disease.
Small amounts of calcium carbonate and gypsum were found under his nails,
along with red and green dye.
Dye, as in?
Basically, chalk.
Connect.
What's the most frequent use of chalk these days?
Construction workers use them as markers.
Pick up possible chalk users from nearby security cameras.
Stop.
Chapter 2 「Dancing Orchid in Chaos」
Say... did the murderer draw this?
Connect.
Show me prior visuals of this scene.
Nothing out of the ordinary for the last five hours,
and recordings before that have already been deleted.
Let's go back to the first crime scene.
Even if you check it out, there might not be anything relevant.
There's only one common thread.
A person leading a normal life commits a
murder because of psychological damage.
And the post-murder investigation
shows no psychological abnormalities.
That other murderer died, though.
Driving people insane enough to commit murder...
It sounds like a power they'd have.
Connect.
No larva signal was picked up, right?
No larva signal was detected at any of the scenes.
It's not possible to drive someone insane without a larva burst.
But there was no larva signal.
Maybe it's a new ability.
That's why I'm investigating.
Connect.
Replay the first scene, immediately after the crime.
Should we go back?
That's right, the doctor said I shouldn't exert too much strength during rehab.
Kiri.
Yes?
You're going to that Fantasy something every day.
No, I'm not saying it's bad.
You've made friends, right?
I smell something sweet.
Kiri?
You don't need to suffer anymore.
How could you do such a thing?
Goodness gracious. Kids these days!
Okay?
Target your voice here.
Start whenever you're ready.
Concentrate.
One more time.
Quon won't come to rescue you.
I know it's tough, but it's for your own good.
That's right.
If you don't master your power,
you'll end up with ugly rashes like Yuri.
Taka-bou!
You're not exactly convincing,
considering that your own arm was injured!
Yeah, is that so?
Your song heals people.
But if you lose control, it becomes harmful.
Oh, training. Nice to see someone so dedicated.
Where's Quon?
Investigating again.
What a busy man.
What are you saying?
You're just too much of a lazy bum!
Oh come on, don't say that.
Anyway, can I borrow her for a bit?
I'd like you to babysit the kids here.
But...
Stay focused!
Well, just let them do whatever they want.
Everyone's having fun.
No.
It just looks that way.
Hara's parents called her a monster.
Takeru's house is under the complete control of the Custos.
All the children here have special abilities.
Here I go!
Hey, I bet you don't know this!
Only primates, which evolved their forelegs into arms, have the ability to throw.
And even among the primates,
us humans are the only ones who can raise our arms and throw something.
This is because we can-
Run away!
Now you've done it!
I'll get you brats!
Try and catch us!
Stop running!
In your dreams!
Why, you...
You're not getting away today!
What are you doing?
Since we're here, I'll take you to the base.
Okay.
Hello, and welcome.
Is something wrong?
You're not hungry?
I'm just happy we can be together.
So am I.
And Tei saw this?
Not exactly.
She picked up a very dark feeling.
We'll follow you.
Is this the best she has?
I don't understand you!
Stop barking!
Another flower.
I wonder if these old-fashioned graffiti are a recent fad.
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid!
What do you want?
Poor... flowers.
Like you'd know anything!
The flowers asked me to do this!
Jeez!
You're eating that again?
For a thousand years.
Cup noodles are the invention of the millennium,
if you ask me.
Yeah.
How many so far this year?
Ten.
There were 23 people I couldn't save.
23 cases!
That's all we've accomplished!
Why do you think the Custos exist?
We're also doing our best.
We didn't summon you to hear your excuses.
You're here to be rebuked.
The cyborg unit has been doing well lately.
We're handling Insania-
Order can only be built on top of sacrifices.
Who has been making the sacrifices to keep order?
We, the Ordo.
How are Delta and Epsilon doing?
Shun and Hizuru?
Delta's and Epsilon's systems are both stable.
Even after I removed their body parts,
their personalities haven't been affected.
I don't see them anywhere.
They're investigating the murder cases, apparently.
They're analysing the similarities one by one.
The ways they approach it are quite unique.
It's very interesting.
So their motive is curiosity.
Their value is in capturing Bestia.
Any other activity is superfluous.
If they continue this too long, erase their data.
That's not very fun.
That would make them no different from AI.
Order can only be built on top of sacrifices.
Brutal stuff.
And this weird scribble.
It's a new pattern.
Maybe the culprit's state of mind is changing.
Perhaps he feels cornered.
Download.
And?
I looked up what flowers represent.
In psychoanalysis, flowers carry a sexual meaning.
Particularly for women.
In Asia, they represent fragility.
In Europe, they represent life.
They also represent beauty and purity.
Flowers don't go well with murder.
Still, most drugs come from plants.
Marijuana is a widely known example,
and heroin is extracted from opium poppies.
LSD is extracted from ergotamine on rye.
Fungi like magic mushrooms and peyote carry hallucinogens.
Though fungi aren't plants.
So flowers can also kill.
Do you smell something?
I can as well.
It's a sweet fragrance.
I sensed it a bit at the last scene, and the one before.
There's a smell associated with the murders?
This could be the so-called Proust Effect.
Proust?
He's a dead author.
Marcel Proust is famous for the novel In Search of Lost Time.
At the beginning,
the protagonist remembers something because of the smell of madeleine dipped in tea.
Now that you mention it, the old ladies in the kitchen were dipping rice crackers in tea.
It's long been known that smells can help recover lost memories.
The effect was named after the author.
Hence, the Proust Effect.
I didn't know smells could do that.
They can't.
But you just said...
The relationship between smell and memory is no different than with the other senses.
However, odours activate the amygdalae, which control some memories.
That's the limbic system.
I'm talking about a part of the brain that heavily affects emotion.
Basically, memories triggered by smell tend to pertain to emotions.
What we want to know is if a smell could be used as a tool to kill.
I was getting there.
The amygdalae control emotions, which includes fear and rage, of course.
If you could control someone's amygdalae,
you might be able to control the person.
I wonder if it's really that simple.
Larva signal, level red detected.
One of our previous targets?
No, it's new.
Then from now on, we'll identify this larva as BF521.
Send in the WTOC.
Roger.
Alpha to Epsilon, move out.
Condition all green.
Perimeter has been blocked.
Operation teams at their positions.
Operation teams, follow the resistance protocol.
Roger.
Operation teams, wait for the arrival of WTOC, then assist them.
We'll wait for their arrival and-
What's wrong?
Operation teams, report your situation.
What the hell is this?
Calm down.
Avoid friendly fire.
B-Seeker has arrived on the scene.
Okay, kick off!
WTOC, kick off!
Formation two-three!
That's as far as you go.
Target BF521, larva burst confirmed.
Switching to phase one.
You monster.
What a pest.
Epsilon's adrenaline level is rising.
A psychokinesis type, huh.
That's not very high on the priority list.
If capturing it proves difficult, exterminate it.
To all units, permission given to exterminate the target.
This smell...
Flowers?
Target BF521 is dead.
Recall them.
Insania detected.
Wait.
We don't have time to prepare for a battle with Insania.
We'll settle the score someday.
Another one that I couldn't save.
Did you smell this fragrance?
Target BF521 drew this, huh?
Connect. Show me the footage of the time this was drawn.
Pursue target BF521 from this point for as long as you can.
Roger.
Wait.
How many minutes before her death was the larva signal detected?
30 minutes.
Show me the footage at that moment.
Roger.
Stop.
Identify the flower.
The flower is Sedirea Japonica.
It has a very unique fragrance.
Is this a drawing of that flower?
It is a 62% match.
Tell the investigation unit to collect that flower.
Roger.
BF521 was responsible for all the cases.
Or... did the flower kill the people?
Let's stop here for today.
You're working hard.
Old man.
Here.
That's for working hard.
Candy.
Why... did you stomp on the flowers?
What are you doing?
Follow me.
Hey, wait up!
Hello!
Here you go.
It's a gift.
Have fun.
Wow!
They're all so happy!
I've never seen a garden this vigorous!
Um...
What's your name?
Kaoru.
I'm Kiri.
Do you like it?
Tei-san!
Did you make this garden?
It wasn't me.
Quon-sama made it.
Quon?
Is he here?
No, he's not here at the moment.
I bet he understands flowers very well.
None of the flowers here are suffering.
They're all loved.
They're not being forced to bloom.
That's why they're all beautiful.
A normal garden is screaming in pain.
None of them are given love,
but yet they're forced to bloom.
They're all crying.
That's... That's why I...
The flowers asked me to do this!
The flowers asked you?
They said they were suffering.
And they'd rather be stomped to death.
You can hear the voices of flowers?
What a freak.
That's strange.
Hey, don't say that!
Flowers can't talk!
Hey, you can't say that!
But that's not normal!
He's a freak!
What a freak.
Stay away!
Yeah!
Why am I so different?
You're weird.
No!
You're the freaks because you can't hear their voices!
Wait!
What a pain.
Does that dog really know what she's following?
The scent is our only lead.
That's not very helpful.
For the moment, it's all we have to go on.
Maybe he's closer to us than we think.
They laughed at me.
All of them might as well die!
Hey, what are you going to do when you find him?
He's killed many people.
Are you going to save that criminal?
Are you saying it's okay for the Custos to kill him because he's sinned?
Then I should be the first one to die.
Quon...
I bear a sin much greater than his.
Did you find him?
Maybe he already went home.
I told those kids not to laugh at other's abilities.
Everyone should just die!
Go crazy!
What was his problem?
You finally found him?
Everyone, I'm home.
Here?
Okay.
He's here.
I know you're in there!
Come out!
I knew it.
What are you going to do? Are you coming in?
Of course!
Look, you...
Aren't you scared?
I can make flowers release scents that make people afraid.
That drive them insane.
Is that how you made them crazy?
They were crazy to begin with.
The flowers are screaming in pain.
But no one is trying to help them.
Still, you can't...
They all say I'm weird!
Come to the Fantasium Garden.
Then you'll...
I was just there.
I hate that place!
What?
Everyone there was smiling. It was gross.
It seemed so fake.
Oh, the garden was kind of nice.
Kind of.
But the people there are terrible.
They say they have abilities, but they laughed at mine and said I'm weird.
They should all go to hell.
You didn't!
I did.
No... Tei...
Tei, can you hear me?
Tei!?
Okay, I'll tell Quon-sama.
The flower that's causing the murders is somewhere in the Fantasium Garden?
Stupid Taka-bou.
The culprit caught him.
Yuri, go to the garden.
What will you do?
I'll save him.
That's you, all right.
Take care of Taka-bou, okay?
I also need to save the culprit.
Quon.
I guess there's no choice.
Thank you for coming to the Fantasium Garden today.
I'm sorry.
We unexpectedly have to do some maintenance.
Yay! I got a balloon!
How's it going?
I don't know.
Too many locations in the Garden have plants.
Find it at all cost, before there's another victim.
Did you find it?
No.
Of course!
This smell...
No, Quon-san.
No!
Shoot! She's losing control!
She's going to destroy our shield.
If that happens...
...Custos will find this place!
What can we do?
Someone needs to stop her!
Hey, don't push me!
You useless men!
Get a grip!
Ow...
Yuri!
Are you okay?
I think I broke a few ribs this time.
How's Kiri-chan?
I think she's fine.
Yuri-san!
You're okay now.
Don't run away.
If you run away, this will happen again somewhere else.
We want to prevent that.
Stay and learn how to control your power.
Okay?
Okay!
Good girl.
Fantasium Garden.
The flower there seems to have failed.
And they've found this place too.
I'm going to get yelled at anyway...
so I might as well do it.
Phalaenopsis. Vuylstekeara. Paphiopedilum.
The collected Sedirea Japonica were perfectly normal?
Yes, nothing abnormal.
Does the effect disperse over time?
Larva signal detected.
The target is BF502.
Alpha to Epsilon, move out.
Miu!
It's dangerous.
Get out of here now.
No. Please do as I say.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to save you before this happened.
Save me?
What are you talking about?
I'm wondering why I never tried this from the start!
Stop!
Only the weak do this!
I'm stronger than anyone.
I can even rule the world.
I can't...
...die.
I see.
Well, how many do you think I should try!?
Stop!
Stop.
You're wrong.
You're boring.
You say the same thing over and over,
and you don't even die?
That's unfair.
Takao!
Ah, so you know him!
Do you...
...think he'll die?
That's right!
You can't do a thing!
Insania detected.
Where?
Near BF502.
Insania and BF502 confirmed.
Formation four-seven.
Gamma's amygdalae are showing abnormal levels.
We're disconnecting him now.
Gamma, disconnected nervous system.
Without Gamma, it'll be difficult to retrieve the target.
It's an interesting ability, but I suppose we'll wait for another time.
Exterminate it.
Roger.
Formation zero-three!
Stop this now!
No!
Now!
You damn monster!
Larva burst, level five.
You should all turn into flowers.
How about I tear you apart the same way that humans tear apart flowers?
You can hear the voices of the flowers?
What about the voices of humans?
I can hear them!
They all say I'm weird!
That's right.
No one tried listening to you.
What you did is wrong.
Though, you just wanted someone to listen to you, right?
Particle gun, fire!
Get away!
If you meet the gardener at the Fantasium Garden,
tell him that it's a beautiful garden.
Tell him yourself!
It's fine.
No one will care if I die.
Don't you dare say that!
Is he crying?
Those monsters don't have human emotions.
Retreat.
We're low on operational funds.
We had a tough time against Insania.
But we gave him a tough time too.
How is she?
I specialize in humans.
So, I've done all I can.
Azuki!
I'm sorry.
Azuki won't die!
She can't die!
What the heck?
I'm hurt too,
but you're all worried about the dog?
She was injured trying to save you!
I know!
We don't have time for your jokes!
Kiri!
You could save her, right?
Kiri... please.
But...
Do you think you'll go berserk again?
You've been training very hard.
Do you think you didn't choose your power?
Well, you're wrong.
Utau kotoba ga itoshii hito wo
The words that I sing to my beloved
The power you wish for from the bottom of your heart,
is the ability you awaken to.
Utano kotoba wa kataru no desuka?
Will the words that I sing speak of it?
Kono sekai atatamete itsudemo
They will warm the world any time
Quon!
I was able to sing well.
I see.
Good for you.
Ookinamirai Inochi no mirai
And a large world is to come in our life's future
That flower...
It's safe.
It's not emitting a dangerous fragrance any more.
No one will make fun of you here.
I'm sorry I never got your name.
Kaoru.
His name.
Thank you.
Kaoru-kun, good night.
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
You're really a kid, if that makes you happy.
Is Tei's power going berserk?
Someone on the outside is trying to infiltrate through Tei's EEG.
You can only regenerate physical wounds!
Not the wounds in your heart!
No matter how cruel the past, it can never be changed.
Who the hell are you?
This is my sister, Lisa.
Towa no Quon, Chapter 3:
Chapter 3   ｢The Complicity of Dreams｣
"Fictional Involvement"