Block off a five kilometre perimeter around Shinigusa Park.
Displaying current image of the target.
Display image.
Image displayed.
Zoom in on the target.
Zooming in.
Intersections have been sealed.
Intersections sealed.
This is Operations Team.
We've arrived at the strategic coordinates.
Roger.
B-Seeker, head to Route 11 from Rena Junction.
Alpha through Epsilon: Condition all green.
Metropolitan Expressway to Iogi, the entrance has been sealed.
Operation time is 21 minutes and 40 seconds from start.
Target BF503 is travelling north through Shinigusa park.
Cannot lock onto the target.
All neighbouring roads have been sealed.
All personnel are at their stations.
Signal strength, please.
Signal strength: 5.991.
It's broken phase six.
How's the bestia?
Target BF503's larva signal is still unstable.
The signal level is above average.
Begin.
Yes sir.
Stay back!
Breaking phase eight.
Larva signal has broken phase eight.
The target's transformation has begun.
Huh?
What!?
Carrier two, lost.
Beginning a sweep around the area.
WTOC has reached its operational time limit.
There are also abnormal readings in Epsilon's brain waves.
Retreat.
Notice to WTOC.
The operation is cancelled.
Begin to retreat.
Roger.
So that... was Insania.
Chapter 1 「The Ephemeral Petal」
Quon-sama.
How is your body?
It's fine now.
Thank you, Tei.
How is he?
Do you mean Yuuma-kun?
He's stable now.
It was fortunate that he hadn't exceeded the danger level.
I see.
That's good.
You may be tough, Quon-sama,
but after your injury last night...
Honestly, I'm fine.
Everyone's already hard at work.
I can't just slack off.
Let's go. It's business hours.
Welcome to Fantasium Garden!
Come in for an enticing dream experience!
We have lots of events for you to enjoy.
Hey, did you know?
Fantasium Garden is also called Shinjuku Cabbage.
I'm Cabbagey!
Morning, Takao.
I'm helping out at the Goat Corner.
I'll be your guide, so come say hello!
When are you going to stop trying the impossible?
You can't save everyone who awakens.
It's just impossible.
Our only fighters are you and Yuri!
Still...
I want to save everyone.
Once you're done feeding them, can you feed the birds?
Okay.
Goat is a common name for an animal of the genus Bovidae Capra.
It usually refers to the domestic variety.
There are seven different varieties.
The most common is the Bezoar goat.
Also- huh?
Hey! Look at this, Quon.
I got a rash again from using my power!
My beautiful skin has a rash!
But we couldn't have saved Yuuma-kun without it.
Hey, can you check over here?
There's nothing wrong.
You're perfectly fine.
Bye!
Hey wait, Quon!
You perverted old man!
How nostalgic.
This place used to overflow with dyed cloth.
The clothes floating in the river looked as if they were dancing.
It was beautiful.
It was a long time ago though.
Is that a music box?
Could I listen to it?
Thank you.
It's definitely a great piece.
Hey!
You've got some nerve picking up girls instead of working!
Honestly!
I'm sorry.
We're supposed to be working.
We'll treat you well, so come play, okay?
And you! Back to work!
Stop, Yuri!
When I sensed her power, that piece was playing.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
She's also awakening.
Targets BF503 and AA001, aka Insania, have been lost.
They're off the radar.
New signal found in west Tokyo.
Beginning surveillance.
Ordo: Latin for order
Ordo has made significant investments in developing and maintaining you.
If you don't accomplish your tasks, then you're just a bunch of useless tin dolls.
Yes, the three destroyed units can't move.
But why did you fail to act, Epsilon?
You weren't nervous on your first operation, I hope?
When I...
identified Insania, I did hesitate for a second.
However...
Will you do better next time?
Am I dealing with a rookie soldier?
Watch what you say.
Sir.
I demand perfection and completeness in every respect.
Please remember that, Rookie-kun.
Sir.
I don't see anything wrong.
What a strange feeling.
When I had a real body, I couldn't
stand to just sit around all day long.
With our current technology,
we still can't surpass the reaction time
between the brain and the nervous system.
However, we can manage everything else in software,
so we can even control emotions like boredom.
All of my physical parts are working fine.
Why don't you try rebooting?
I don't want a malfunctioning unit that acts on emotion watching my back.
The only reason you can be sarcastic is
because your brain is even working at all.
You're a nice person.
Not entirely.
I'm treating you guys as objects when you still have emotions.
If there's a heart in my body,
then it's made entirely of tektite.
Keep your heart strong.
You have a wonderful ability.
However, you'll only make everyone sad if you abuse it.
Don't worry.
If you wear that, you can suppress your power,
and you also won't be a target.
If you train here for a bit,
you'll be able to control it perfectly.
You... can say that because you're able to control it.
But I...
I can't!
I'm human, just like you.
I make mistakes.
But I don't ever give up.
So make me a promise.
Promise me that you won't abuse your power.
I...
Just stay here.
This is your home.
The Fantasium Garden is now closed.
Please come again.
Man, I'm tired.
What to eat today...
We have yakisoba today!
Thank you for always helping.
Where's Quon-sama?
Miu, did you use your power again?
I see.
He's with her.
Look. This is the cafeteria.
They're all your friends.
Yuuma-kun!
Have you recovered already?
Just take your time, and learn to get along with them.
What's up?
Did Qu-chan and Tsukki have dinner?
Jougasaki
Japanese
Dance
School
Thank you. Sorry.
Kiri.
Oh, never mind.
What a beautiful voice.
You have a magical voice that makes everyone happy.
I believe your granddaughter has lost her voice due to mental trauma.
Don't worry. You'll be able to talk again,
and even sing that song.
It's definitely a great piece.
Larva signal detected near Shinjuku-ku.
It's not in the database.
It's a new individual.
Signal level: blue.
Here you go.
It might not look appetising, but it tastes good.
The vegetables were grown in the greenhouse here.
It's very important to eat seasonal vegetables,
so that you get plenty of...
Here we go again.
Hey, you have food on your face.
Signal level has risen to yellow.
Naming the target BF509 due to the rising levels.
Let's end this, now!
Yes, we believe it's the girl.
Okay. Thank you.
Quon-sama is on his way.
Taka-bo, when it gets bad, save him.
He's on his own.
Larva signal continues increase.
WTOC, stand by.
Roger.
WTOC standby level raised from four to three.
Begin loading units Alpha through Epsilon.
Larva signal rising further.
It's only a matter of time until it breaks surveillance level.
Signal lost.
Cannot find its location.
Location not confirmed.
WTOC, cancel standby status.
Use caution
when entering
the intersection
Thanks for working so late.
I'm introducing a new friend to your garden.
What is it?
Oh, it's a persimmon.
When I slipped into the warehouse back home,
I found the seed in my great-grandfather's belongings.
I never thought it'd actually sprout.
Oh, the persimmon tree that was in your garden.
I remember climbing it with you.
No, you made me climb it!
You always brought up my great-grandfather and made me do the impossible!
How's the boy from last night?
Holding up.
What about you?
I want to protect her too.
Kiri.
Aren't you tired of taking care of me all the time?
Why don't you go outside to play now and then?
Don't mind me. Go out and play.
I want to be alone sometimes too.
Front of Fantasium Garden
Flan, you're back?
Here, have some tea.
Kiri-san, make yourself at home.
I know!
I'll give you a tour.
Due to the owner's policy, most employees are youngsters like us.
Let's go.
Seeing is believing.
Enjoy yourselves.
Hardening of the skin...
He's a new type.
This is your home.
Brother!
Wait up!
Well, hurry up, or we won't make it in time!
I know that!
Each of the five areas have a virtual attraction,
and there's a shopping mall on the second floor.
They have lots of Cabbagey's goods-
Hey, we'll go there later!
Towa.
Thank you.
It's definitely a great piece.
I'm Quon.
You?
Her name is Kiri-chan.
Jougasaki Kiri-chan.
Kiri-chan?
What a nice name.
Japanese International Medical Centre
Kiri...
Don't worry.
You'll be able to talk again,
and even sing that song.
I wish... you'd never been born!
Grandma...
Kiri, you have the voice of an angel!
Utau kotoba ga itoshii hito wo
The words that I sing to my beloved
Utano kotoba wa kataru no desuka?
Will the words that I sing speak of it?
Oh, no. What should I do?
How is she?
She's in cardiac arrest.
Contact the ICU.
Kono sekai atatamete itsudemo
They will warm the world any time
Grandma?
I knew it.
Your voice is magical.
Grandma!
Thank God!
Thank you, Kiri.
Jougasaki-san!
Eh?
My...
New larva signal detected.
It's BF509, the one we lost last night.
Another signal.
It's BF503, the one Insania seized.
Send out the WTOC.
Roger.
B-Seeker, loading complete.
Permission to launch granted.
I thought he'd calmed down.
No one could understand how deep his wounds really were.
Yuuma-kun isn't safe right now.
We have to find him quickly!
Locking onto BF509 in 530 seconds.
BF503 is heading south toward Shibuya.
Team WTOC has passed route seven.
Getting ready to surface.
We have two targets.
We'll split into two.
Beta and gamma, go after BF503.
Delta, Epsilon, and I will take BF509.
All hands, equip with Selten sword.
Beta and Gamma, change into heavy shields.
Roger.
Entering operational range.
All hands ready for deployment.
Connection complete.
Condition all green.
Alpha through Epsilon: eject from B-Seeker.
Arriving at normal roads in two minutes.
Order is necessary for preserving world peace.
If someone breaks that order...
...then they are evil.
Two signals.
Yuuma-kun and Kiri-chan?
I think so.
What are they up to?
They're sealing off all the roads.
Are they using those cyborgs too?
Yes, they're on the move as well.
Are they taking both of them at once?
What?
We can't save them both at the same time!
Quon-sama?
Don't try to be a hero.
You can't save them both.
Which one are you going to save?
Well, hero?
Both.
I want to save them all.
And that won't change in a thousand years.
BF503 found.
Following.
A five hundred metre perimeter around Shinjuku West Exit has been sealed.
All units at designated locations.
My voice...
Quon used his power.
Which one is he going to?
She's still nearby.
Begin searching.
Roger.
No!
Stay back!
Man, give me a break.
If I hadn't been close to you, I would've been hurt.
Yuri-san, what was that?
Your voice...
It was your power.
I'll explain later.
Now, hold on tight.
Identified Insania.
Proceeding to process two.
How are they?
Checking now.
Yuri.
Can you hear me?
Tei?
I made contact with Kiri-chan.
Can you get Quon to come?
They're inside this building.
Switching from larva detection mode to thermal mode.
I see. They're a fun bunch.
Switch to normal vision.
We'll find them with our eyes.
Roger.
Honestly.
Hurry up, Quon.
What are you people?
We're attractors.
According to Kannazuki, we've awakened.
We can change our feelings into power.
Change feelings into power?
It's cold.
Why do I feel so cold?
Yes, and you're one of us.
What? I am?
Stop!
Please don't kill me!
Are they fighting each other?
Yuuma-kun.
Calm down.
Look at me!
Look.
I'm human, just like you.
But still...
I want to use my power to save everyone.
I'm sure your power will be helpful too.
Which one won?
Insania?
Quon-sama!
Please, don't overwork yourself any more.
Damn it.
Quon, you idiot!
Hurry it up, you bonehead!
They... transported?
Hey.
If I happen to die with some horrible expression on my face,
would you close my eyes?
Come on.
I can't die looking ugly!
I don't think I'll have that kind of time.
Of course...
You lost them?
What do you mean?
They're here!
I see.
So that's how it is.
Taka-bo!
Are you okay?
No.
I'm at my limit.
That's for skipping training!
Be quiet.
Kiri-chan, hurry up.
Take this chance and escape.
Okay!
Now, come on.
But...
Hurry!
Coming!
Where is he?
Delta, are you still functioning?
Yes, just barely.
He was a tough opponent, just as the data said.
However, that'll end today.
Get away!
-Alert- Intruder
What's going on?
The security system at the factory has activated, apparently.
What's the strategy team doing?
Looking into the cause.
Local police and firemen are heading towards the scene.
We're not ready to deal with the Japanese government yet.
Retreat.
Successfully hacked the factory's security system.
We did it!
Ow, that hurts.
Be more gentle!
Just be quiet!
A-Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
Be quiet! You can't do anything by yourself.
That's enough!
You're exactly right.
I can't save everyone by myself.
But you came.
Thank you, Takao.
And you too, Yuuma-kun.
I'm sorry.
I broke our promise.
In return, you learned how to use your power justly.
Isn't that right?
But...
I need to practice more.
Then we can practice together.
Yeah!
Hey guys!
Good work!
What should I do?
You're also one of us.
I want to save everyone, no matter what.
Those who fear their powers.
Others like you and Yuuma-kun who don't know what to do.
Everyone.
And they're all helping me do that.
So I'd like you to help me as well.
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
Because I heard your heart moaning in pain.
Order can only be built on top of sacrifices.
The flower doesn't go well with murder.
There were 23 people I couldn't save.
It wasn't me.
Quon-sama made it.
They don't have human emotions.
He killed many people.
Are you going to save that criminal?
Towa no Quon, Chapter 2:
Chapter 2  「Dancing Orchid in Chaos」
"Orchid Dance of Chaos"