Be careful.
You're defenceless in your sleep.
You're attracted to a strong will.
Please don't.
You'd be sending me into a world of darkness, where I couldn't move my limbs.
Figured anything out, Novice Detective-san?
They laughed at me.
All of them might as well die!
No, Quon-san.
I can't...
...die.
How about I tear you apart the same
way that humans tear apart flowers!?
It's an interesting ability, but I suppose we'll wait for another time.
If you meet the gardener at the Fantasium Garden,
tell him that it's a beautiful garden.
Which one?
A little higher...
That yellow one!
Okay.
Got it!
Onii-chan, you're awesome!
Congratulations.
Here.
Yay!
It's ugly, but it's cute too.
Thanks a lot, Onii-chan.
You're really a kid, if that makes you happy.
What the-?
Crap!
Lisa!
Lisa? Lisa!
Onii-chan!
Lisa!
I can't breathe. Onii-chan!
Lisa, where are you?
Onii-chan!
Lisa!
Were you dreaming?
I can tell by looking at the EEG.
I'd be interested to hear about your dream.
I was dreaming of my past.
About my parents and sister from ten years ago.
You were dreaming about your family?
It's not unusual.
But I guess I shouldn't expect something special just because you're a cyborg.
Not unusual...
I wonder if that's the right phrase to use to describe it.
Geez, more interruptions.
Chapter 3 ｢Fictional Involvement｣
Tei is watching over the boy.
Quon is fighting the enemy.
Where's Yuri?
Sorry I'm late.
Is this the boy?
Please take him.
You monsters!
Stop!
Epsilon?
Epsilon's been deactivated!
What's the cause?
Checking as we speak.
Something happened when he tried to recover the target.
Ow!
Be a little gentler!
This is as gentle as I get.
This is for skipping out on training.
If you hadn't messed up, I wouldn't have needed to do anything!
I'm grateful for what you did.
Thanks, Taka-bou.
You won't fool me with your shallow thank-
Ow! That hurts!
We can't see her right now.
Now, you should all go back to your rooms.
But...
Is Tei-san okay?
Yes.
Dr. Wakatsuki's checking up on her.
What's she doing right now?
Can't we go inside and see?
Tei may not look it, but she's strong.
She'll be back and healthy before you know it.
So let's do our best to not make her worry before then.
I know, but...
Kiri-chan, please take care of the kids.
How's the boy you saved?
He's also doing fine.
He must be exhausted from using his power.
He's sound asleep.
That's good.
Now, you should all go back to your rooms.
We'll let you know as soon as Tei gets better.
Okay.
That's a promise!
Let's go.
Dr. Wakatsuki, how is Tei?
I don't know why she isn't waking up.
But judging by her EEG, she's in a dreamlike state.
She's dreaming?
Yes, I can identify a pattern resembling PGO waves.
They stimulate the hippocampus and cause people to dream.
What about his physical functionality?
The data output doesn't show any abnormalities.
I wonder what exactly happened at the scene.
Alpha.
Sir.
16:46. We confirmed target BF463's larva burst.
We were dispatched as soon as the location was pinpointed.
17:03. We arrived on scene.
17:06. We attempted to recover the target
and became involved in a fight with Insania.
At that time, Epsilon was fighting as backup.
Allow me to replay Epsilon's data.
Epsilon switched over to recovering BF463 plus two others.
He then froze at the moment of contact.
What will happen if he continues in this state?
Well, if he remains asleep like this...
...it's basically the same as brain death.
Eventually, she'll die from malnutrition.
That's...
Where am I?
What?
Oh, I need to find that boy.
What is this?
I'm coming!
I'll save you!
Tei!
What's happening!?
Midori-kun?
What's wrong!?
Her EEG's suddenly become unstable.
Her heart rate's rising!
Tei, stay strong!
Welfare Corporation Nursing Home
No!
Yuri!
What's wrong?
No, stop.
Yuri!
Get a grip! Yuri!
I...
You saw something?
It wasn't that simple.
It felt like I was actually sent back to my childhood.
Is Tei's power going berserk?
Berserk?
What does that mean?
Tei can communicate telepathically using her power.
But she can also uncover people's pasts and emotions.
If she wants to, she can amplify them and confuse others.
Then did she-
Tei...
His EEG has become unstable.
His biological parts are at 40.6C.
It's possible they'll stop functioning.
Any way to avoid that?
By erasing his memory. Formatting his data might work.
Then do it.
But that would destroy his personality.
If that happened, he'd lose the advantages of being a cyborg and be a mere android.
I think you'll be able to gather the new data you've always sought.
Very well.
I'll prepare for formatting.
Preparations complete.
Initiating format.
What's going on?
Her EEG's becoming unstable again.
But it's a different pattern this time.
Hold her down!
Damn it!
Cancelling format!
What's going on?
I've identified a wave pattern belonging to a third person.
He seems to have somehow synchronised with Epsilon's EEG pattern.
What are you saying?
I'm analysing the wave pattern as we speak.
I've found a match!
The larva's pattern is the controlling mind.
I see!
One of Epsilon's targets must be interfering with his brain.
It's hard to believe, but Epsilon seems to be
telepathically linked with one of the targets.
That would mean...
Can you trace the link?
Technologically, it's possible.
But it involves much higher risks than the formatting.
In the worst case, Epsilon will never...
If we can trace the link, we can locate their hideout.
That includes Insania.
Doesn't this sound like the perfect chance?
But what about him?
A small sacrifice for the greater good.
Roger.
Attempting to trace the link.
Beginning trace.
I hope that you're at least dreaming about your family.
What's this!?
What?
What is it now?
Ryo, what's going on?
The med room's console is behaving strangely.
Someone on the outside is trying to infiltrate through Tei's EEG.
Her power burst probably linked her with one of them telepathically.
What?
At this rate, it's only a matter of time until we're discovered.
As I thought.
They're using very complex routing.
Tech division, can you finish the tracing process?
Roger.
10% tracing rate.
They're fast.
Why are they so fast?
Dr. Wakatsuki, can you cut Tei off from the medical system?
I can't right now!
If I do that, she'll die in less than a minute!
I see.
Then I'll somehow try to buy us some time.
Ryo, sorry, and thanks.
We're being interrupted.
I'm not surprised that they discovered our intrusion.
Find a way to keep going.
Roger.
Ryo made these?
They're dummy chips that imitate Tei's EEG pattern.
I could only prepare 40 of them.
But I'm also setting up fakes at access points around the world.
With more places for them to find, we'll have more time.
But we'll still be found eventually.
I asked all my animal friends, but there are still 23 chips left.
Leave it to me.
I'll go scatter the rest.
I'll help as well.
I can do this alone.
You figure out a way to wake Tei up.
I'll go to buy us some time.
Yuri.
I can't help, you know!
I know!
Your job isn't to use your power multiple times.
But you'd better do the best you can when it really counts!
Miu, let's go.
Well, if you really want me to, I could take one.
Oh no!
She's become unstable again.
Quon?
What's up?
It's this boy.
I can feel it.
I hear his faint voice from time to time, mixed in with Tei's consciousness.
Then, is he also connected to Tei?
Tei probably chose to remain in her
mental world in order to save this boy.
If that's the case, perhaps I can talk to her through him.
But your psych power isn't very high.
If you mess up, you could join them!
You know I have to do this, Seiji.
You can only regenerate physical wounds!
Not the wounds in your heart!
Still...
I want to protect everyone.
Tei, and this boy.
To do that, I have to.
Quon.
Take care of everyone for a while.
Okay.
Do be careful.
Well then, time to wreak some havoc!
New relay points detected on the map.
This will change the tracing time.
So that's their plan.
They're trying to confuse us.
They're scattering fake signal sources around the globe.
We'll need to check each one of them to locate their hideout.
Larva signals detected.
Fifteen signals detected in district 23,
all at the same time.
Transferring authority to the information division.
Activating surveillance protocol.
Initiating surveillance of the target.
Boy, I am a hard worker.
No. I'll never forgive you.
Where are you? Come out!
Tei!
Okay, which one next?
Um...
Tei!
Tei, it's me.
Can't you tell?
Who are you?
What do you want with Lisa?
Tei, who is he?
Who the hell are you?
This is my sister, Lisa.
She's not Tei!
I see.
This is his memory.
Tei, you're being consumed by his memory.
Remember yourself!
You unleashed your power in order to save that boy.
And now, for some reason, you've become trapped in his memory.
Both the physical you and the boy are in critical condition.
You can't stay here any longer.
Get out right now!
Everyone's in danger!
Tei!
I...
Enough of that!
I've already told you that her name isn't Tei!
If you keep spouting nonsense, I'll teach you a lesson!
O-Onii-chan!
What!?
Who are you?
Lisa, no!
This... This isn't...
Tei, get away!
You're trapped inside his memory!
No!
Lisa! Lisa!
Damn it! What did you do to Lisa?
You surprised me.
I thought you were all just chunks of metal.
But I guess you have memories too.
This isn't the real me.
Who are you?
Where did you send Lisa!?
This is just a fantasy you've created.
Enough of your lies!
I'm not handing my sister to anyone!
I'll get Lisa-
I won't let any bad guys live!
What's going on here?
Yeah, I'll get rid of the bad guys.
I'll be a superhero.
You're...
Wait!
Nii-san. Nii-san!
Nii-san, wake up!
Nii-san!
Towa.
Geez, Towa. What took so long?
I ended up falling asleep.
I didn't have any trouble finding the herbs,
and look at what I found on the rocks.
What's that flimsy thing?
It's rock tripe.
It only grows on rocky cliffs.
It takes hundreds of years to get this big.
Really? You're so smart.
Everyone knows about this, and that Granny Chiyo loves it.
Granny Chiyo, huh?
All I get from her are boring lectures.
She's worried because you're not trying to improve your power.
I don't need power to get by.
Well, it's a lot better than using it for something bad.
Now, let's go back and help get the festival ready, or we'll-
What was that?
Oh no, we need to save him.
Be careful.
He might be from the village.
That doesn't matter!
Towa!
What a terrible injury.
Towa, he's from the village!
D-Demon!
Please, I'll give you what I've caught, so spare me!
I'm not a demon or a ghost.
I'm just going to take a look at your injury.
Stay still.
It's broken.
Now, can you pray hard for the pain in your leg to go away?
Just wish from the bottom of your heart for your leg to be healed.
I'm sure it'll get better.
Hey! Don't tell me you plan to use your power.
Shush!
Now, please trust me.
Towa.
It's all better.
T-Thank you very much.
The road back down the mountain is steep, so be careful.
Hey, why did you use your power on a villager?
You know it's against the tribal rules.
I just wanted to save someone in trouble.
One of these days, I'm sure we'll stop caring about all that stuff.
I'm sure of it.
Towa...
Now, we'll get in trouble if we don't hurry. Let's go.
This conversation...
I've had this before.
W-What's going on?
One of the larva signals matches our records.
It's BFS02, who works alongside Insania.
Their jamming system appears to be in effect,
and we can't locate her larva signal.
Dispatching operation teams A through F for invasion.
It's a fine move on their part for buying time.
Let's deploy the teams to lure out Insania.
Quon, take care of Tei.
Ryo.
I've confirmed it on my side as well.
The organisation is close to locking in on Yuri.
That idiot.
What about infiltrating the system?
So long as the dummy chips are in effect, we'll manage.
The signal from number 16 disappeared?
And 31! 6!
Are they destroying the dummy chips one by one?
A cat?
The signal's around here.
Leave no stone unturned.
How's it going?
No problems so far.
His personality is disappearing, as I feared.
They've already destroyed six of them.
If we don't disconnect as soon as possible,
they'll pinpoint our location.
Quon.
Quon!
If the elders find out you're slacking off again,
they'll give you another lecture.
Oh, you already got the festival pendant?
Anyway! The adults are getting ready to worship the holy tree.
I know it's a little late to say this,
but do they really need so many people?
Why don't they just use their powers to do that?
It's against the rules to use it outside the festival.
You can only use it during the power exhibitions.
Geez, I know that.
Still...
people won't always think that way.
Look at this!
See, you're doing great!
I can do it really well when I'm around you.
I did it!
I did it, Towa!
Good job, guys.
At that rate, you'll do just fine during the exhibition.
Now then...
Nii-san, shall we get going?
Go? Go where?
You forgot?
You promised we'd go herb picking.
No, didn't we already-
I'll get rid of you.
Who are-
Wait, could this...
Could this world be?
We'll get nowhere if we just go on like this.
How are things at your end?
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
Everyone has
.
returned already
I see.
Then we're just depending on Yuri.
Dr. Wakatsuki.
How long will she stay like this?
If Tei's power is responsible for her
current state, as Ryo-kun suggested,
trying to solve this medically will turn out badly.
Then all we can do is just stand around and wait!?
Well, Quon is our only hope.
Wait!
Nii-san. Nii-san!
Nii-san, wake up!
Nii-san!
Towa.
Geez, Towa. What took you so long?
I ended up falling asleep.
I didn't have any trouble finding the herbs,
and look at what I found on the rocks.
What's that flimsy thing?
It's rock tripe.
It only grows on rocky cliffs.
It takes hundreds of years to get this big.
Really? You're so smart.
Everyone knows about this, and that Granny Chiyo loves it.
Didn't we already...
What's gotten into you so suddenly?
We've had this conversation before.
This isn't reality!
It's him!
Look! Right there!
Nii-san!
Stop! Tell me what's going on!
That was a memory from my distant past.
But it felt like I was just living it.
Was Yuri reacting to the same phenomenon?
Then... Tei and that cyborg too...
I get it!
This world isn't... It's...
Tei! Where are you!?
You can't stay here!
I'll kill you.
I'll get rid of all the bad guys.
Onii-chan, thanks!
You're really a kid, if that makes you happy.
You're not current with the times, Onii-chan.
That's why no girls-
Who are you?
I haven't seen you around.
Which school are you from?
At first, I thought this was a fantasy world you had created.
But I just came back from my own past.
This is a fantasy which that boy has fabricated.
You and Tei are trapped within this world.
Remember who you really are.
You can't stay here any longer!
What's his problem? He's crazy.
Lisa, let's go.
Tei!
Lisa?
I...
Don't get in the way.
Don't get in the way!
What?
Just one more.
Oops.
What's the situation?
I hate to tell you this when you're doing a good job,
but they're destroying the chips one after another.
How are Tei and Quon doing?
No progress yet.
Well, I guess I have to buy us even more time.
Yuri, what are you trying to pull!?
A moving target will buy us more time.
Stop! It's too dangerous!
You're already being tracked!
Geez, thanks for believing in me.
You should know I'm good at running away.
Yuri. Yuri!
That idiot.
Under construction
Target BFS02 is heading north-east.
An access point is also moving with the target.
So childish.
God, I'm tired.
I guess this is the best I can do.
Taka-bou!
You came for me?
Let me tell you...
I'm not doing this just once.
I have to do it twice to go back.
Taka-bou! Taka-bou!
Goodness, what did you come here to do?
New larva signal detected in the Shinagawa district.
It's moving with BFS02.
Insania's more likely to show himself if two of his friends are in danger.
Send out the WTOC.
Any contact from those two?
It looks like something happened.
They're both headed towards the Shinagawa station.
I see.
How are the dummies doing?
21 left.
I see.
It's me.
Yes.
I know this is sudden, but...
Y-You're...
Why?
Oh no!
Miu!
Keep it together!
What happened?
It was only for an instant, but I saw Quon.
I saw Quon consumed with rage.
What?
Is he connected with Tei?
What was that?
Oh no.
Quon.
Shit!
Yuri and Takao are surrounded?
And the dummies?
18 left.
Quon...
So you are Insania!
Quon-sama...
What the heck did you guys do?
We didn't do anything, really.
Tei's desire to protect and your hatred linked with the boy.
That caused him to wander into the darkness in his heart.
We won't let you take him!
I'll kill you.
Who is that?
Where are you? Where did you go?
I'll get rid of the bad guys.
Over there?
I'm coming!
Wait!
Where did you hide it?
I know there are some left!
Stop!
He'll wake up!
Why?
You promised we'd go to the festival!
Don't worry, I just tripped and fell.
I'll become a superhero!
I'll get stronger and get rid of the bad guys!
So this is all your fault!
I... never even got to touch my family.
Or even talk to them.
She reads people's minds.
Everyone hated me, and I was always alone.
That's just sick.
She's a monster!
I'd only heard the sound of festivals. I'd never seen one.
But you showed me what a festival was.
It was fun.
Truly strong people don't think about defeating someone.
They think about saving the weak.
But... I...
Don't worry.
We'll also help.
I... I...
Let's try to be strong together.
You'll have a lot of friends too.
You won't have your way.
I won't allow you monsters to-
You still haven't realised?
Realised what?
Your sister,
when I synchronised with her, I found out.
You're locking your past away.
W-What are you saying?
Stop talking crap!
No matter how cruel the past, it can never be changed.
Shut up!
I volunteered for this body to get rid of monsters like you!
The past doesn't...
Stop!
Onii-chan!
Help me.
Onii-chan.
Lisa! Lisa!
Help me, Onii-chan!
It's hot!
It's hot, Onii-chan!
No.
No! Onii-chan~
Lisa... I...
You're back?
Epsilon has awoken.
As a result, we've disconnected.
We failed to locate their hideout.
What about the larva bait?
We're closing in on them,
but the target has the upper hand in terms of speed.
Get all the operation teams on their tail.
We're done destroying the dummies.
As of now, capturing Insania is the highest priority.
Roger.
I hope you won't fail to entertain me.
It looks like the dummies no longer matter.
You're okay now.
I'm sorry I caused so much trouble.
How's Yuri?
I've already taken care of it.
You don't need to worry.
So she's in danger.
Quon.
You should already know.
You can't stop me.
You never change.
I'm out of breath.
We're doomed.
Quon!
Get Takao out of here now!
But-
Now!
Quon!
I won't... ever go through that again.
I have to...
I have to... protect everyone!
Beta, Gamma, and Delta are damaged.
Such a desperate struggle.
What?
Explosion detected inside the enclosed area.
It appears there was an accident in one of the constructional facilities.
An accident?
Are you sure it wasn't intentional?
The investigation team is checking the cause.
The operations team's barricade was set perfectly.
Firefighters and police in that jurisdiction are headed for the scene.
We don't have time to conceal the incident.
Only someone on the inside could pull off a stunt like this. And...
I see.
Sorry for the trouble. Thanks.
I'm glad there was no permanent damage.
I'm sorry.
I'm just glad you understood.
Thank you.
It seems they got pretty roughed up yet again.
Sorry, but I'll have to check on you later.
Did you see it too?
Yeah.
Was that real?
It definitely felt real!
It was scary.
Yuuma.
Quon, have you killed people?
Yes, I have.
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
Epsilon is unstable.
We should format his data.
Doesn't that mean you can fall in love
again, despite living for a millennium?
We shouldn't have saved him!
Roger.
We'll destroy Epsilon.
Then I shouldn't be forgiven.
You guys aren't human.
I used the traitor as bait.
Towa no Quon, Chapter 4:
Chapter 4 ｢The Roaring Anxiety｣
"The Roaring Anxiety"