I have killed people,
but that's why I'll protect you...
Insania.
Stop!
Tei!
That's not what you would do.
We should get raw data from the larva.
Onii...
Destroy Epsilon.
We met in the dream.
This isn't a mission.
It's a hunt to kill every single one of them!
Run, Quon!
Quon!
What have you done?
You caused an explosion at the centre of Shimauchi!?
The Defence Minister's position will be in jeopardy!
No, this isn't just about the Defence Ministry.
The entire political field itself is in danger!
What do you think we should do, Kamishiro-kun!?
Custos's people only disclose their rationale in Ordo's presence.
What did you say?
This operation has been approved by all members of Ordo.
Whether it's been approved or not doesn't concern me,
but the politics of Japan-
That's enough!
But...
While you think only of Japan, Ordo considers the whole world.
Their core members sanctioned the operation.
We have no choice but to obey.
Sir, how do we go public with this information?
Just say that terrorists attacked or something.
You figure it out.
The Defence Ministry will take full responsibility for the incident.
But sir!
This is a favour to Ordo from us.
Ordo will not be indebted to anyone.
Well then Kamishiro, this one is for you.
I heard there is an open spot in Ordo's Council.
I believe you are mistaken.
It's safe froM
here on out
I see.
We've lost Fantasium Garden, huh?
Are you all right?
Yuuma, you...
Is this my power?
So your powers aren't just tossing bubbles around.
This is no time to rest.
We need to rendezvous with everyone.
From here on, you'll have to climb.
Quon-sama, Shun-san.
There's no need to worry about him.
He's definitely not dead.
Chapter Five「The Return of the Invincible」
Epsilon did it?
Yes. It looks like he took out one of the inspectors and fled.
Our cameras and guards were tracking him,
but unfortunately he escaped.
In that condition?
How was he still alive after the blast?
Such a shame.
If we still had network access, we could've obtained crucial data.
Shun.
Is everyone asleep?
They've been walking and climbing for hours.
They fell asleep from exhaustion as soon as they hit the bed.
It was one heck of a day, after all.
Kannazuki-san, who is this person?
Ah, her name is Sanada-san.
She helped us a lot when we created Fantasium Garden.
She's an old acquaintance of mine.
It's okay, she knows who we are.
Are you going somewhere?
I have to do something.
At this rate, we won't be doing anything.
Oh, where are you going?
I'm going out for a bit.
I'm going out!
Okay, have a safe trip.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Where is Epsilon now?
We lost him, but he should be located soon.
We're searching for him in the vicinity.
If we dispatch the cyborg team, we can-
The infiltration team shall withdraw.
But...
No bodies were found in the amusement park.
We'll use the cyborgs' abilities to counter
however many creatures are on the loose.
Understood.
Kannazuki.
Kamishiro-kun, it's been a while.
What business does the boss have here?
Does a member of Ordo need a reason to visit a branch organization?
Would you like something?
Have you heard?
The sudden change in one drunk settler's actions has caused 10% of the Japanese people to stop drinking.
Whatever, you did something unimaginable by bombing the city.
How many were you able to kill?
None of them.
But we were able to destroy their base of operations.
You seem confident for someone who failed.
What can you do about a plan approved by all the other members?
Did you let Insania escape?
I've no need to answer such questions, what are you getting at?
Alpha confirmed his death.
Quon is... dead?
Is there something wrong?
No. His body?
His body? Probably destroyed in the bombing.
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Even so, why the sudden interest in Insania's status?
Ordo will protect world peace.
People will look forward to a
peaceful future under our guidance.
That is why I shouldn't need to explain it to you all over again.
Are you saying that you have the
Hundred Kings Council's permission?
Apparently not.
I can raise a member drafted by the Council of Ten to the Hundred Kings Council.
They know about it.
But still they can't detach me from them.
Oh, I wonder why.
I don't think I'm obligated to answer that.
Shall I tell them that after becoming the Custos commander,
you prioritised the enemy's capture over their elimination?
I have their consent.
How about the fact that no one was
found where they were reported to be?
You shouldn't make fun of the one in charge.
"I wonder where they went,"
is what I would've liked to say.
What happens to the creatures is of no concern to me,
but I have a growing interest in the ongoing operation.
After all, we're dealing with a large number of them.
That is...
Member Kannazuki, now it's my turn to ask the questions.
They sure are lively.
Old man, are you not coming back?
What will we do now?
"What" indeed.
We have no choice but to stay here.
I wonder how long we'll stay.
We were always relying on Kannazuki-san.
Ah, this is just great, even Quon is dead!
Taka-bou!
You all feel the same, don't you!?
Quon can't die.
He faced many dangers before.
And he always returned.
Well, then why isn't he here!?
Quon, you bonehead.
The Fantasium Garden Guard Squad, are you aware of it?
Who knows.
We reached K&N after going through a number of dummy corporations.
K&N is also connected to the recent Shinagawa incident,
and its explosion.
Member Kannazuki,
you're its chairman, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Corporate manager Nagatomo-san told us all about it.
No way, not Nagatomo!
It's within the boundaries of the Juunebu teachings.
Even if we torture our subjects, we don't kill them.
Kannazuki-san.
Let's hear about it in detail.
What if Quon really died?
That...
No, it's like Wakatsuki-san said.
We need to prepare for the worst.
He might be dead.
I don't want to think about it.
Yuri...
I don't want to think about that sort of thing!
I think I'll leave.
Since Fantasium Garden is gone, and Quon isn't here,
there's no reason for us to stay together.
I want to go home for now.
I want to see my parents, whom I've troubled.
Takao!
Sorry, I...
I'll stay here, since there's no reason to return.
I don't like to think about it.
If Quon isn't coming back anymore, I'll make a place like the Garden.
Yuri...
It was fun, wasn't it?
Everyone was laughing and playing all day.
That's right! if we combine our abilities-
Would that be the right thing to do?
We've thought about this before, was the garden the right choice?
What are you talking about?
You see, we hid ourselves from the world,
and couldn't even return to our homes.
Was that the right thing to do?
I don't think it was wrong!
I didn't mean to say it was wrong.
But I think we should give it some thought.
To leaving the garden, that is.
How did the chat go?
It was exciting.
What about Epsilon?
Even though he has such a wound,
he has broken through all the infiltration team's attacks.
It's too bad he isn't connected to the net.
It seems that I need to use WTOC.
S-Stop it!
Fire!
Stop it Epsilon.
Surrender immediately.
Hizuru, huh.
Epsilon.
Hizuru, these people we gathered aren't monsters.
They're just normal kids who laugh and play.
What are you saying?
They are monsters.
Monsters...
A monster would be something like me.
If I surrender and return to Custos,
I'll be experimented on right away.
Shun...
What do you plan to do?
I've been given orders to capture you.
Hizuru.
Right.
Oh well, you leave me no choice.
Sto-
Shun...
You can't catch me!
Give my stuff back!
Man, I'm beat.
What is it?
I did it back then, but all I can do now is make bubbles.
You were practising?
You put a lot of tea in the cup.
It reached the point where...
...adding any more would cause it to overflow.
I had a dream.
Mother was crying.
She wanted to see me.
Quon-san's not here and Kannazuki-san isn't back either.
I wonder what will happen to us.
Hey, did you see Tei and Kiri?
They went out.
Went out? Where to?
Kiri had to visit her grandma, and Tei went with her.
I did the laundry.
Thank you. I feel better now.
Sorry for making you worry.
It's all right. All I want is for you to be happy.
You see, I am weak.
And all I do is make you worry.
Sorry about that.
It's not like that at all. I'm sorry.
There, there.
Tei-san, was it?
I'll leave this girl in your care.
I can manage now that Helper-san is coming by.
What this girl needs the most are friends.
Grandma!
I'm counting on you Tei-san.
Understood.
What a kind grandmother.
Just act naturally.
Excuse me, we would like to see your identity card.
Here you are.
All green, it's verified.
Sorry for stopping you.
Not at all. Let's go.
Excuse us.
I don't know for how long that will work.
Don't run, and keep a distance from me.
Okay.
It's all red, isn't it!? After her!
Now what? The road to grandma Sanada's house is blocked.
Kiri-san, do you think Quon-sama really died?
Do you think Shun-san died?
Same here. If it's them, they will surely come save us.
I will use my powers from now on.
They might come looking for us, and the situation could get dangerous.
Are you okay with that?
Quon-sama...
Please save us, Quon-sama.
All repairs done.
Adjustments done. Thanks for the effort.
So, you let Epsilon escape?
I am extremely sorry.
He was injured and yet you couldn't catch him.
I wanted the data, so I told her to capture rather than destroy him.
Capture?
We're not dogs.
We got a larva red alert in the Shinjuku area.
Use the infiltration team to block the surrounding area.
Roger, dispatching teams D and E.
Shun-san.
Are you all right, both of you?
Yes, I'm glad you're unhurt as well.
What about the other children?
They were evacuated safely.
Thanks goodness.
Shall we be on our way?
Yes.
Piercing the nails with hot needles sounds painful.
Kannazuki-san, please tell me.
What is this "Tears of Time" that the Kannazuki possesses?
I don't know about such a thing.
Oh my, did it break inside? How unfortunate.
Even I don't like resorting to such methods.
What are the "Tears of Time"?
Why are you alone not monitored, even among the Council of Ten?
"Respect," or so I'd like to say.
Stop it!
I said stop!
My healing... finally caught up.
I wonder what's causing this painful suffering.
That's right, I fell in a hole, and then...
It can't be...
It can't be this.
May I help you?
The password is: "Iconoclasm".
Roger. "Iconoclasm" program in service.
What's wrong?
What happened?
The cause is unknown.
The system has crashed.
Give a high level order.
We can't. One has already been authorized.
Why?
It's Iconoclasm.
What?
Sorry Ryo, but I have to release the Protector.
So everyone is fine?
Quon! Thank goodness.
So you were safe after all.
But how?
Don't go that way, Quon!
You sure know your stuff, Kannazuki-san.
Tei! Kiri-chan!
We were worried because you were late.
I thought you were captured.
It got dangerous for a moment.
Someone came to our rescue.
Shun!
You came back?
It seems you need treatment again.
Ryo, will you lend me a hand?
Sure.
Is it okay for me to be here?
What are you saying?
You're more than welcome!
You're our friend as well.
Where is Quon?
So it's only you guys?
I see.
Wait!
It sure is lively even though they lost their home.
It's because they're together.
As long as they have each other,
their feelings won't change wherever they are.
I guess so.
Quon, no.
The "Tears of Time" would be too-
Quon! Where are you?
Quon! Quon!
Why?
Please... listen.
Why!?
Seiji, why did you hide it?
Quon.
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought of you as my friend.
Why?
Listen, this is something the Kannazuki family has been-
Thanks for leading us here, Kannazuki-san.
Kamishiro! Why you!
Anyway, this is...
Who are you?
As expected of Insania.
Alpha confirmed your annihilation.
Who would have thought you were alive.
Ah, I forgot to introduce myself.
Kamishiro Genji, the commander of Custos.
Are you sure you should be fighting me?
Haven't you asked yourself why the cyborgs aren't here?
The more of you that die, the better.
Their destination is Sanada-san's building.
If I'm right, that place assisted in creating Fantasium Garden.
Kamishiro, you bastard!
Everyone is there.
Please stop the attack!
And why should I do that?
I have no reason to comply.
Quon.
Let him be.
Now then, Kannazuki-san,
let's hear more about this "Tears of Time", shall we?
The EC car has surfaced from the underground junction.
Okay, now...
Everyone, gather around me!
What an interesting power.
Gamma, use area pulverisation.
Roger.
Shun.
Formation 13.
13 is an unlucky number.
One who is swayed by emotions will not be forgiven!
Now, tell me.
You got your freedom from the Council of Ten by using this as a trump card,
am I wrong?
You don't need to know.
I don't think you have the luxury of choosing.
The one who you call Insania, Quon, has a little brother, Towa.
Oh?
Towa, perhaps the person with the greatest ability of all.
If his power is activated it will cause a huge catastrophe.
It was around a thousand years ago.
It was to protect his friends.
He feared the consequences of his own powers more than anyone.
Out of fear of his own strength,
he sealed himself.
Towa locked himself up in this place for a thousand years,
sunk in sadness.
Kamishiro, you're thinking of using
Iconoclasm and taking me in, right?
But, I had seen through that much.
I called you out here!
These people aren't monsters.
They're just normal kids.
Shun...
What's so funny!?
How pathetic.
You spent so many years hiding that and now you are trying to destroy it yourself.
If you were fine with that, you would have just pushed the switch.
Sorry I've been keeping it from you, but I also have abilities, you see.
What!?
But my ability is a little different.
I can turn another's abilities into my own.
There's no way he can die, right?
What's going on here?
Quon!
Ah, Quon-sama!
Quon-sama!
I may have gotten old, but you haven't changed in 60 years.
Your beauty hasn't changed since then, Mayumi.
Formation 0-1!
Roger.
Hizuru! I don't want to fight you!
Hizuru...
This is...
S-Shun!
Man, that's cool!
Shun-san.
Is that his full power?
Alpha, orders.
Check your limits.
Shun.
Don't falter.
The children...
What about the kids you gathered?
Don't tell me, you bastard!
This is the power I took from Saki.
How weird.
I didn't think it was possible to burn bodies too...
No way!
How nice!
Now I get it.
Towa's power amplifies the abilities of others.
Now I know why Ordo has been turning a blind eye to your actions.
A recovery team is headed this way.
If you want to get out, now is the time.
Wait, Kamishiro!
Gamma: Function ceased.
Alpha: Movement dropped to 40%.
Delta: Unstable mental status.
What on earth!?
Quon!
Delta, I'm changing the battle plan.
Are you functional?
R-Roger.
You've done enough.
Sir!
They're just hard-headed people after all.
What!?
He suddenly appeared out of nowhere.
Commander, why are you here?
You think you can question me?
Fall back.
But...
Delta, that's an order.
Roger.
For this greeting, I will show you my powers.
Kamishiro!
Grandmother, hang on!
Grandmother!
She's not dead.
But, she might have lost something valuable as a human.
Why you!
Easy now.
I've yet to explain.
My power lets me manipulate other powers, making them mine.
Kamishiro, so you had abilities as well!
Then why?
Have you ever thought about why your powers exist?
Or where they come from?
Why are you accepting persecution?
Do you accept the belief that you are fools without power?
What are you trying to do?
There was reason I had been hunting your kind for Order until now.
That was, to save you.
You'll understand once you come to headquarters.
I haven't killed a single person.
Are you satisfied staying like this?
You live your lives in fear, hiding in the shadows.
Do you intend to keep doing so forever?
Don't you want to return home?
I could meet mum?
Yes.
Don't let him trick you!
He was the one who ordered your capture!
But if it's me, I can give you a new future.
A new future.
A future where you can smile with your parents.
Won't you come with me?
Your parents may be killed by Ordo.
Takao-san.
Taka-bo!
Sorry, but I want to see my mother again.
I won't ever meet her if I stay with Quon.
Takao, don't be fooled!
Mama may be killed this way.
I don't want that.
Mother.
H-Hey, everyone!
I want to see everyone again!
Now, now.
I don't want my thoughts looked into.
Tei!
Kamishiro, let those kids go!
Bakao!
Quon...
Everyone, I'm sorry.
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
Even if you've lived for
hundreds or thousands of years...
I...
...shut up. Shut up!
You saw it, didn't you? Those kids are like normal humans!
Those who disturb order are nothing short of evil.
Why does he resist? Why isn't he waking up?
Give Towa back, don't you dare dishonour his name!
Towa no Quon, Chapter six:
Chapter Six          「Eternal Quon」
"Eternal Immortality"