Towa, perhaps the person with the greatest ability of all.
Quon can't die.
Well, then why isn't he here!?
Surrender immediately.
Shun...
Please save us, Quon-sama.
The password is: "Iconoclasm".
My healing... finally caught up.
Don't go that way, Quon!
Why?
Why!?
What about the kids you gathered?
Don't tell me, you bastard!
I could meet mum?
Tei!
Kamishiro, let those kids go!
Operation accomplished. Retrieving operatives.
Headquarters, roger that.
Please confirm official activity.
Roger, confirming.
No police or military movement.
The situation is being protected.
Everybody, please stay here.
Quon!
What do you intend to do?
I need to save Towa, Tei, and everyone else.
Wait!
Seiji!?
What are you thinking?
You can't face them alone.
We should combine our strength and come up with a plan.
Towa is in the Custos headquarters!
How should I get in?
Please tell me!
Were it so easy.
I could simply download their headquarters blueprints.
But with the current security crackdown, that'd be rather difficult.
I might be able to infiltrate their system by using the data you recently stole.
If I access the security system from there, I might...
Ryo, please do it.
I'm sorry.
I should apologise for keeping the secret about Towa.
No, you were just protecting him.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Just what are you talking about?
Something from long ago.
Humanity back then controlled powers, such as yours, as natural abilities.
However, due to sudden changes,
people who could use them became rare.
And in time, tribes that couldn't use them became dominant.
As a result, those without abilities feared those with these powerful abilities.
Youkai, Mononoke, and other folklore spirits,
Quon's clan became hated in various forms.
They were forced to leave all normal human settlements and live elsewhere in solitude.
It's just like with our Fantasium Garden.
Even so, Quon's clan opposed the conflict and hid their powers.
So then, why?
For a period there was a tradition amongst warriors and nobles to hunt down youkai and other monsters to raise their status.
On that night, the night of the yearly festival,
they attacked our village.
So that's how it all started.
For unknown reasons, Towa became sealed in the crystal and Quon became immortal.
My ancestor found him alone on the battlefield and took him in.
Ever since my childhood I have wondered:
"Why does he continue to sleep like this?"
"Is it because his sins have still not been forgiven?"
I'm going too!
You're going to rescue Towa, right? I'll come as well.
And we have to get Tei and that bonehead back as well.
Yuri...
Me too.
Takao-san was truly grateful when I erected that barrier.
So please!
Everyone... I'm sorry.
Chapter 6         ｢Eternal Quon｣
Can't sleep?
You know, my grandmother used to be a dance teacher.
She was really amazing.
Once taught by her, anyone could dance beautifully.
I like its song.
Thank you. My father and mother made it for me.
I'm also worried.
About what this power of mine really is.
But one day I realised:
"Of course, it must be the same for my parents as well."
Whether you write a song, cook delicious food, or paint a picture.
Those sorts of things are also abilities.
Everyone must have wonderful abilities of their own.
Towa.
You must be worried about everyone, and about your little brother.
On that day.
I was the only one who wasn't in the village.
I ignored everything and climbed into the hills.
With this I can get away for a bit.
Man, I sure messed up.
I couldn't protect them... neither the village people or Towa.
Towa possessed a gentle heart.
One of these days, I'm sure we'll stop caring about all that stuff.
I'm sure of it.
Back then I swore to myself...
...that I would never repeat those mistakes.
I'm sorry for keeping these secrets until now.
I'm somewhat happy now.
You're telling me about yourself.
You always seem to be somewhere far away.
Quon, you...
Even if you've lived for hundreds or thousands of years...
...I-I would...
Ryo says that his preparations are done.
These are the blueprints to the Custos headquarters.
There are responses here and here.
Are those Tei and Towa?
Most likely.
I'll lead the infiltration team.
That Kamishiro guy hasn't come to tell us anything yet.
Doesn't this look like a cell to you?
Say, will we really meet our mamas and papas?
Say, Takao-san.
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up.
Shut up!
90 seconds until operation start.
Security systems shut down.
Opening the gate.
What?
What happened?
No way, they detected the hack!
Hizuru!
I'll take care of this, you guys forge on ahead.
But...
There are things I have to finish myself.
Go!
Still not done?
I finished the connection.
However, her mental state is rather unstable.
I can't say whether she'll be a good booster.
I don't care, start it.
Roger.
It'll be better if you don't resist.
That way it'll be easier on you.
Yuri, go ahead!
I can't tell anyone's locations with this anymore.
Looks like we'll have to search by ourselves.
Leave them to me!
I don't want to fight you!
You saw it, didn't you? Those kids are like normal humans!
They will disturb order.
Those who disturb order are nothing short of evil.
Hizuru.
Quon-sama, everyone.
Increase the output.
Going any higher is dangerous!
We don't really care if she lives or dies.
Roger.
I just heard Tei's voice.
Yes, I heard it too.
This way!
Why does he resist? Why isn't he waking up?
We can't hold Insania down,
requesting permission to abandon C-Area.
Roger. Permission granted.
Shun.
I regained my heart.
And so will you.
Don't you see it?
You too, haven't yet...
Hizuru!
You're in the way!
This is the final strike!
Why?
Don't get me wrong.
All I wanted was to return the favour.
Now, I can rest.
Hizuru!
Insania infiltrated the central tower.
He's currently traversing Area 3-1-3 of Block 5.
Towa, where are you? Towa!
Taka-bou...
Towa!
Dear me, bringing him here was all good and well,
but he crystallized this place as well.
Kamishiro!
I guess this place won't be able to hold out much longer.
Well, fortunately Towa has awakened.
As long as I can acquire his power,
I don't really care for this place anymore.
I will not hand Towa over to the likes of you!
Oh?
Nii-san.
Nii-san!
Towa.
Towa!
Don't, Nii-san!
Towa.
Towa!
Takao-san...
What's that supposed to be?
You're going to come with us.
Move it already!
Is that an order from Kamishiro?
Do you actually believe what that guy said?
You know he's the person that has been after us, don't you!?
I want to go.
I want to go home!
If it's for that, I...
Takao-san...
Aw, what a drag.
Move it, I have to go rescue Tei.
Out of the question!
Taka-bou!
Stop it!
Does it look like Kamishiro cares about making our parents happy?
Can a guy who wanted to kill us really bring happiness to anyone?
Tell me, Takao-san!
What?
Insania is currently-
What's wrong?
Systems down! Even though there is no physical damage...
...accessing the main server is impossible.
What's going on here?
The block has dissipated.
It seems that something happened to their system.
HQ, come in. HQ.
Any luck?
It's no use, there's no connection.
Communications with the defence team severed.
Can't recover the system.
All control has been taken over by Ordo!
What's this?
This is...
The committee has made their move, huh?
So without dying there's only suffering, huh?
W-What should we do?
Everyone, can you hear me?
Ryo?
That's good. You're still okay, right?
Not really.
I want you to take this calmly.
That facility is currently undergoing its self-destruct sequence.
Self-destruct?
How did that happen?
I don't know who activated it.
Though, since their system is down,
I'm able to get in and bring our communications back up.
Takao-san?
What will happen to us now?
With things like this, we'll drown here.
I want to meet my papa and mama.
Takao-san...
Damn it all!
Everyone, gather around me.
You two too, hurry up!
That's too much for you, taking so many at once.
Be quiet and hurry up.
I was a fool.
Let's go.
It got both my legs.
Takao-san!
You overdid it.
Shut up.
Tei!
Tei, hold on!
Do you recognise me?
Yuri...
Yuuma-kun too.
Thank you.
What's that supposed to mean?
They really intend to bring this place down.
I see now.
They want to wash their hands clean of us.
I'll do it.
Everyone, gather around me once more.
I won't allow it.
Do you want to break your neck?
I should pay for my foolishness and for putting everyone in such danger.
Don't you want to meet your family?
So let's get home alive, no matter what.
Without leaving anyone behind, okay?
That's it!
Yuri, I found you an escape route.
I got it.
Anything from Quon or Shun?
Tei, please let all the others know.
All the others?
There's no way through, it's already flooded with water.
What about the emergency hatch?
It's locked and won't open.
Right now, something...
The self destruct sequence cannot be halted.
The countdown began.
All emergency corridors have been locked.
I can't find any way to escape.
The defence team is in the same situation.
Just what should we do?
What was that?
An escape route?
That's a larva's voice.
We made it to the T-junction.
Turn down the right corridor.
Turn right at G_006.
Can we believe them?
The information is accurate.
If we traverse the debris we can reach the surface.
As of this moment we abandon this base.
Head for the escape.
This way!
The path ahead is blocked,
turn back and climb the stairs you came by earlier.
The stairs at B_204?
What should we do?
We can't rule out the possibility of a trap.
It's blocked beyond here.
It seems wiser to trust them, so hurry.
Nii-san.
Towa!
Nii-san!
Just now...
It's useless. Soon, Towa will be a part of me.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Towa!
Quickly now!
Stop it!
Turn around that corner.
How could this...
Even if get past the debris, the gate on the other side is locked.
Ryo!
All other routes were submerged from the last explosion.
That gate was the only chance.
This can't...
I will...
You can't, it's dangerous.
But-
I'll do it.
I've always been running away.
From this power and from those who wield it.
I wasn't able to protect Lisa.
Far from it, even.
I, with my own hands...
If I had protected my little sister...
...she would've been able to pursue any kind of dream, right?
And one day, she might have been able to find happiness.
However, Lisa and her future,
I incinerated them with my own hands.
But I won't run anymore.
I will push forward, because there's nothing to fear or be ashamed of.
A human's potential is unlimited.
And your abilities are without a doubt the human potential.
And nobody can block your path forward.
Shun-san!
The younger brother heard his older brother's screams and awoke.
You danced fabulously to my expectations.
And as I said, Towa will become part of me.
No, stop.
No... Nii-san!
Towa!
Nii-san.
This is bad!
Yuri, Tei!
Is there no way for us to save those children?
It's more than obvious that Ordo is behind this.
That we are even in their plans
means that we should be careful.
I see.
All of you, please stay safe.
Yuuma-kun.
You saved us, thank you.
You're a capable guy.
This is great, I can feel even more power than I expected.
Give Towa back, don't you dare dishonour his name!
Towa never wished for a world like this!
I will never let you do as you wish!
I see, so you can't understand my actions.
Well, that makes you nothing but a hindrance.
Quon!
What is the meaning of this?
The commander's a larva?
Well, let's raise the curtain on this concert!
Yuuma-kun! Tei?
Hold on Tei-san!
Kannou-san.
Stop it!
But-
It's okay, just calm down.
If you take hold of your emotions, you can control it.
No. Stop it! Don't shoot!
Good. Why, isn't this great?
Unlimited abilities will be born from our combined power.
Towa...
Everyone...
I...
I was...
...once again...
...unable to protect you.
Toki wa kimi wo michibiku ookina mirai
There will come a great future to lead you
Everyone.
Mawaru toki wa kibou wo mottekuru
When it comes, it will bring hope
I'm sorry.
I gave it my very best effort.
Kinou ga kanashikute tachidomaredo
Yesterday was so sad that it stopped me
I tried so hard.
Kinou wa sugiteyuku sotto sotto
But that yesterday will slowly, slowly pass away
I get it...
In that case...
...I'll have to try a little harder!
That's it, it's not over yet!
How very persistent.
Quon!
What an impressive immortal you are.
But you're still just a one trick monkey!
Quon!
Quon-sama!
Is that all you've got?
Finally, I can reach you!
Towa.
So you were actually alive.
Sorry for being away so long.
It was... because my heart was so weak.
You're wrong Nii-san.
I should be the one to apologise.
On that day, I was the one who made your powers awaken as they did.
And it was also my fault that the village was attacked.
When the village was attacked, I became overwhelmed with fear.
My mind could only focus on rescuing myself.
Fear lurks in everyone, you can't blame yourself for that!
That's not all of it.
I called for you from within my heart.
Though I couldn't help anyone or save anyone,
in the end I just thrust those emotions onto you.
I was the one that made you dirty your hands.
I'm nothing but a coward!
In that case, there's only one thing that we should do.
Together, let's finish what we started a thousand years ago.
All this power is just here for me to rule it!
Thank you.
Towa.
Don't go!
Towa!
No, as if I'd hand it over to anyone!
I'm also a larva. I'm one of you, you see.
D-Don't you protect your own kind?
Quon, have you killed people?
Liar!
Murderer!
I'm scared, don't come closer!
The last of the destruction went over nicely.
Kamishiro being a Larva was unexpected.
Kannazuki's defence was too easy to see through.
This simply means we've been
given a new task from this point.
We will need to construct a new order.
Who is worthy of constructing the new order of the world without anyone even noticing?
We of Ordo.
Please come over here.
Excuse me, could you tell us what happened here?
We have absolutely no idea what is what anymore.
All right, please bear with it for a moment.
Everyone, we've come to pick you up!
What about Kiri-chan?
She stayed home with the kids.
It's so good to see you're all okay!
You sure gave it your all, thank you.
Don't touch me so casually!
Just who do you think I am?
All we want is to treat you.
Man, what a handful.
Where's Quon?
Quon saved us all.
He was really awesome.
He was even faster than Takao-san's teleport.
Quon.
This, could it mean?
Towa was released.
From his oh so long imprisonment.
It finally began to move again...
...this stopped time of mine.
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!