No!
Help me, Onii-chan!
I won't let any bad guys live!
It's hot!
It's hot, Onii-chan!
I just wanted to save someone in trouble.
One of these days, I'm sure we'll stop caring about all that stuff.
What was that?
Oh no.
Quon.
Quon-sama...
I...
I saw Quon consumed with rage.
No. No!
I have to...
I have to... protect everyone!
So you are Insania!
Quon, have you killed people?
Yes, I have.
Chapter Four   「The Roaring Anxiety」
The truth is always cruel.
He's an enemy, yet he's one of us.
Your condition is unstable.
How's Epsilon doing?
His adrenaline and dopamine levels are fluctuating.
He's in an unstable condition.
What happened to him?
We're not sure.
Are you analysing his data?
We are, it's an easy task to analyse visual and aural data.
Though, this time it's a cerebral problem.
Are you saying you're not familiar with emotional problems?
Epsilon's unstable.
We should format him.
I told you before: that would be boring.
Formatting him would be a simple task.
But this is the perfect chance to gain data about emotional struggles.
Just think of how this might benefit future technology.
Fine.
You can use him as your toy for a while.
But when I give the order, format him immediately.
Here, let me wipe you clean.
Hey!
You liar!
Stop, you two!
Ryo-san.
Rule number two: No fighting.
I know!
But he said that Quon has killed people!
I saw it.
That's all a lie!
I saw it too.
Me too.
I don't know anything about it.
Does anyone know the truth?
I saw it, but I won't believe it.
Are you okay?
It's dangerous if you run off like that.
Murderer.
Quon, you've killed people, haven't you?
I'm sorry. That was only meant for me.
Though you saw it somehow.
If you could, I'd like you to forget about it.
No, I want you to remember it,
so that you won't become like me.
Will I become a monster one day, too?
No you won't.
Just remember what you saw and never become like that.
I have killed people,
but that's why I'll protect you and do everything I can.
I thought you didn't like these things.
Sometimes I have an unstoppable urge to eat them.
Boy, that was good!
Thank you.
Thank goodness.
Quon, you've been living forever, right?
Yeah.
You've lived a long time,
yet you still regret what you did in the distant past.
When I realised that you don't have all the answers, even at your age,
I felt good about being human.
Still, doesn't that mean you can fall in love again,
despite having lived for a millennium?
Was that so funny?
Sorry, I didn't mean to laugh.
That just came out of nowhere.
Thanks.
I read your report.
Is their headquarters really in Zero Area B?
Yes, though that's just a hypothesis.
Over the years, we've found these Zero Areas, which don't emit any larva signals.
And we've confirmed that there are three of them in the capital.
Furthermore, when Insania captures larvae,
they can no longer be traced or detected.
It's possible they have a force field of some sort that erases larva signals.
Do any of them exhibit force fields?
No.
We don't know why these Zero Areas emerge.
It would require a vast amount of energy to create a force field strong enough to thwart our radar.
It would be impossible to create a force field in all three locations.
Then the other day, case C73 happened.
Cancelling format!
I've identified a wave pattern belonging to a third person.
We've been unable to pinpoint where the interference wave originated.
But we can make estimations using probability and Zero Area B is very close to the most probable origins we've calculated.
So the headquarters of an organization
aiding Insania is somewhere in this area?
Yes.
Quon-sama...
Millennium Tree...
...you've been watching him all these years.
Please, tell me his pains.
Quon-sama?
Watch it!
What an idiot.
No one will help you when it really comes down to it.
I need to save them.
Who made you king?
Yeah, right, you can do it.
Just don't even try.
That's the least I can do... for all the sins I've committed.
Quon-sama, where are you?
Can you hear my voice?
Why do you close your heart even to me?
Hey Missy, who you looking for?
Should we help you?
No thank you.
We're saying we'll help.
Please let me go.
Hey, isn't this cute.
Stop!
Tei!
Larva signal, level red detected.
It's a new target.
Can your toy move?
I think Epsilon will be okay.
Send out the Cyborg Unit.
What's the matter?
It's just a hair pin.
If you want it back, then play with us.
Get away from me!
What, you don't want it?
That's not it.
You're in danger.
What are you saying, anyway?
Hey! How the hell do you know about my girlfriend's body?
What?
Hey, what are you saying?
Didn't you hear him?
He said she looks just like my girlfriend!
That she has the same curves!
What do you mean by "Work something out, dimwit"?
Why would you say that?
I didn't say anything!
Wait.
Let's calm down.
Something is wrong.
Did you hear voices?
Please stop!
Don't look at me!
If you look at me, you'll be looking into your own hearts.
You'll see your ugliest thoughts.
Huh?
I actually never liked you from the start!
Damned Dad, I'll never forgive him!
Please don't send your hatred to me.
I'll only strengthen your feelings.
This is your fault?
Extermination of the infected, complete.
Proceed immediately to formation 0-5.
Will you be okay?
I can do this.
N-No.
Stay back.
Quon-sama!
Insania.
Proceed to formation 2-7.
Quon-sama!
Onii...
Onii-chan.
Quon-sama.
Stop!
Tei is not your sister!
No! No! No!
I didn't kill my sister!
Larva signal level yellow detected.
I-It's...
What? Is it a new target?
It's Epsilon.
We've detected a larva signal from Epsilon.
What?
Should we disconnect him?
Wait!
That's not what you would do.
We should get raw data from the larva.
Shun!
The signal has reached level red.
Destroy Epsilon.
Roger.
Relaying to WTOC.
Destroy Epsilon imme-
Wait!
If we disconnect him right now,
we'll lose a larva we could monitor.
Tell them again.
Cyborg team, destroy Epsilon immediately.
Roger, we'll destroy Epsilon.
Delta, what's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
Fire.
Activate infrared sensors.
It's not working. They jammed the signal.
Damn.
You okay?
Get it together.
But Quon-sama...
W-What are you doing?
He's also one of us.
We have to save him.
He's our enemy.
No! Not right now!
Goodness.
Insania and three other larvae are on the move.
We'll pursue.
No. Even if they're injured, four's a big number.
We'll have to rethink our strategy.
Return to base.
Isn't it best to hit them when they're weakened?
Return to base!
Roger.
This is ridiculous.
His nervous system is expanding and eroding his mechanical tissues.
I can't handle this.
Midori-kun, it's all yours.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Why in the world did you bring him here?
We didn't have a choice,
considering the circumstances.
Don't use big words!
You always do as you please.
Couldn't you have talked with us before you brought him back?
I'm sorry. I should have, but he was hurt.
You should've just left him there!
He's one of us!
Still!
Be quiet!
We're in the middle of emergency surgery!
Not like you need to save him.
Look, I'm a doctor!
A doctor treats everyone, enemies and allies, alike.
They're all patients, understand?
Do you guys know the phrase "The lion spares the suppliant"?
And I've heard that Bedouin, a desert tribe,
welcomes anyone as guests, even if they killed their parents.
Still...
If we throw him out of here, he'll lose his place in this world.
You, most of all, should know how painful that is.
So, how was he able to pass all of our tests?
About case SR23Q, in which his family was killed.
We looked into it.
However, there was little evidence since everything had been burned.
So we had to trust Epsilon's testimony.
I never thought he had altered his memories.
You didn't investigate?
We did.
We investigated carefully using all types of scanning tests.
However, we didn't find anything wrong.
We're currently strengthening the scan
tests and will retest Alpha through Delta.
That's a given.
But why did he become a monster now?
We believe the reason is the EEG interference incident.
Our guess is that the interference caused his forgotten memories to resurface.
His ability must have resurfaced along with the memories.
I see.
In any case, your team is fully responsible for this failure.
Do you understand?
O-Okay.
Where am I?
Oh, you're awake?
You've been unconscious for three days.
Don't try to get up yet.
I don't know why, but your biological and mechanical tissues are fusing together.
So don't try to move.
Where am I?
Well...
This is the Fantasium Garden.
It's you!
We met in the dream.
This is the hideout that Custos is looking for.
Quon! Are you sure you should be telling him?
I know, but he's like us.
No, you don't!
Not everyone wants to save him, you know.
Kazami Shun, we will welcome you as our comrade.
Quon!
Are you sure?
I might report this to headquarters.
Well, with trust comes the risk of being betrayed.
Are you... saying you'll trust me?
Can I be alone?
Sure.
You still haven't located Epsilon?
He's completely disconnected.
We believe there's some sort of jamming in effect.
Isn't it the operator's job to find him anyway?
Who gave you permission?
Commander.
A cyborg needs permission to enter here.
Who gave you permission?
Go back.
I'll overlook this just once.
Is Epsilon still missing?
Even if he was found, I'm not obligated to tell you.
Excuse me.
A doll should know its place.
And a doll should be useful to people.
As Epsilon was.
What are we going to do?
That's what we need to discuss!
We shouldn't have saved him.
It's all your fault, Quon.
Do you understand?
He caught our friends,
and even killed them!
You remember how it felt when they were killed in front of you!
And now that's in the past because he's awakened?
Well, I also shouldn't be forgiven.
That was a long time ago!
But they're the same sins I committed.
Maybe we should give him a chance too.
Why?
He should be killed!
Isn't that right?
Then will you condemn him?
Will you condemn him and tell him he's to be executed?
None of us can condemn him, so we should give him a chance.
A chance for him to admit to his sins and repent.
You're so kind, Tei.
But kindness isn't always right.
Kindness sometimes corners a person.
utau kotoba ga itoshii hito wo
The words that I sing to my beloved
utano kotoba
Will the words that I sing-
What are you trying to do to me?
It sounded like you were in pain.
Is this your ability?
I had a full system maintenance just the other day.
Well, we can never be too cautious.
The data in my body parts is always linked to the data centre.
What should we be cautious about?
That's right.
The truth is, you might go looking for
him by yourself if I don't keep you here.
Even if I go out to look for him,
I'll be monitored constantly and you
should be able to locate me at all times.
And look at our situation with Epsilon.
You're really worried about him, aren't you?
It's natural to worry about a comrade.
So even cyborgs lie.
Your adrenaline level is rising.
If you had a heart, I'm sure your heart rate would be increasing.
Hey!
Come and get me!
Give it back!
I'm over here!
Hey, come back-
That's enough playing for today.
It's time for dinner.
What are we having today?
Curry?
They're just kids.
I...
We also have the right to live.
We just want to live. That's all we want.
But your existence threatens order.
Order?
Is that more important than people's lives?
Can you feel it?
It's warm.
Maybe we're different from normal people,
but we're human.
You aren't human.
Then what are you?
Your hand is so cold.
I'm...
...a monster.
We're monsters, right?
Yet we're human.
And so are you.
You're just a little different from normal people.
What are you doing?
It's a chip for security.
If you keep this on, they won't find you. It will also help you control your ability.
May I?
Thank you.
I don't understand.
Understand what?
Why did you give the order to destroy Epsilon?
You probably wouldn't understand, but it was all for order.
Order?
Is that more important than people's lives?
It's delicious!
We just want to live. That's all we want.
I'm...
...a monster.
Are you feeling better now?
Yeah, the Kiri girl sang for me.
Why did you come get me?
It must be suffocating to stay inside that room all day.
And there aren't many people out and about after the park closes.
ima wa kako kako wa ima
The present is past, the past is the present
It's been so long since I last saw the moon...
...or even just cared about the night sky.
He's headed your way!
Watch my back, Epsilon!
tatoeba kizuna ga mada torimodoseru nara
As if it's ever possible to regain our bound
She's practising.
Practising?
hibi ga sari imi mo naku
As days pass without any meaning,
Yes.
We're all afraid of our powers.
What do you mean?
Like trees, for example.
Just as tall trees root deep into ground,
nagareru dake de itsumo subete wa yume
it was all a dream as it fades away
we need to be as strong as our powers, or we'll fall.
That's why they practice, to learn how to control their powers.
yami no kanata ni sake nozomi himeta hono
Build a fire filled with desires for my dark beloved,
Otherwise, their powers will devour them.
Larva burst.
Hm?
No, it was nothing.
I see.
They were just fearful of their own powers and panicked.
atsuku migoto na hana mune ni sake
let my heart bloom as a nice, warm flower
I was trying to grow taller without rooting myself in the ground.
No, I wasn't trying. They made me.
kako no soto soto wa kako
Past the outside, the outside is past,
Are you okay?
Stop that!
nagarete simae itsuka aishita yume
flow and go away, my once beloved dream,
Why did you stop me?
He killed Yuriko-chan!
Like she was some kind of animal!
You can't do this now.
daremo mitakoto ga nai
the thing nobody has ever seen
Tei, you idiot!
sorewo sinnjitemitai
I wish everyone could believe
I hated all of you.
katachiarumono to ikite ikouto
that we should live with things with shapes
I always believed that one of you killed my sister.
That's why I volunteered for Custos.
Their mission was to hunt people like you.
But...
The one who killed my sister was...
hoshi wa nanndomo ochiru
Stars will fall numerous times
I can't say that I understand you.
soshite shizuka ni inoru
and I will pray quietly
You'll have to carry this darkness yourself.
Just as Quon-sama has his own darkness.
katachiaruga yue ni yasashiku saite moete
Whether it has a shape or not, grow gently... burn away
I was supposed to be fighting monsters, but I was one of them.
And I've become an even uglier monster.
Don't move.
I can't stay here.
Still, where can I go?
I can't go back there.
But I can't stay here.
He's leaving.
Oh well.
He chose this path himself.
Won't they find out about this place?
I altered all his network-related programs when we healed him,
so we should be fine.
We've received Epsilon's location data.
Just as planned.
Switch his control over to the main system.
Roger.
This is odd.
His location transmitting program isn't running.
How are we catching this?
We have multiple programs on him.
Even if one program is altered, a different program gets executed.
You knew?
Did you think they'd accept a thing like Epsilon?
He's a monster above all monsters.
Is that why you purposely allowed Insania to take him away?
There's no better use for a traitor than as bait.
We've gained control of him.
Access his visual and aural data.
Figure out where he's been.
Roger.
Put the cyborg team on standby.
Make sure they can leave as soon as we find something.
Cyborg units Alpha through Delta: standby.
We've accessed Epsilon's data, and we're just about done analysing.
We have his current location.
He's at a park in Shinjuku.
There's a facility named "Fantasium Garden" nearby.
Cyborg team, move out!
Now, let's have Epsilon launch the first blow.
By himself?
Insania would be there too.
It's a very risky mission.
This isn't a mission.
It's a hunt to kill every single one of them!
Stop. Stop.
Please stop.
Don't worry. Come with me.
We've lost Epsilon.
Their jamming shield is blocking transmissions.
We're fine.
I altered his program.
He should destroy the shield system on his own.
Don't... Don't make me do this!
Please!
Wait!
Stop, Shun!
Shun!
Shun, please stop.
Insania detected.
We have Epsilon back on radar.
It seems we've successfully destroyed their shield.
That makes it easier for the cyborg team to move.
Display Epsilon's visual data.
A kid like that was Insania?
This "Insania" thing is intriguing.
Stop, Shun!
I'm not doing this!
My body's moving on its own!
What?
They're trying to make us fight!
Everyone, hurry up and get away!
Where's my bear? Kuma-chan?
We'll find him later.
Please stop!
I don't want to do this either!
Kill me!
Kill me, or I'll attack the children!
I can't do that!
If you don't, people will die!
Good job, Epsilon.
Don't call me by some codename! My name is Kazami Shun!
You are Epsilon.
Proceeding to exterminate Insania.
Run, Quon!
They're equipped to kill you!
I can't run away.
I have to protect the kids.
She got my ribs.
Concentrate!
This won't proceed as it usually does.
Quon!
As if I'd fall for the same trick twice.
Here, I'll break more of your ribs.
When did these get here?
I knew I should've killed you back then!
Run!
Or I'll end up killing you!
Larva burst confirmed.
We've lost control of Epsilon.
That's ridiculous!
It's unbelievable for him to cut off our controls on his own!
It's unbelievable for a larva to be one of our cyborgs.
There's no change in orders.
Destroy the traitor cyborg.
Tei, take him and run.
What about you?
I'm going to fight the ones I should be fighting.
Damn it.
Shun!
Oh, no. I'm your opponent.
Not bad.
Quon!
Insania exterminated.
Exterminated?
Retreat.
Sir, there are many of them here.
We should capture them.
I said retreat.
Roger.
That was easier than I thought.
We're not going to hunt them?
I've changed by mind.
Quon...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul that seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
raiu ni utare totsuzen mezameta honnou
雷雨に打たれ 突然目覚めた本能
I was struck by a thunderbolt, suddenly awakening my instinct
risei wo oshinokete moetagiru no sa
理性を押しのけて 燃えたぎるのさ
It burns on, pushing aside my sensibility
kioku no kabe ni kakikomareta shinjitsu wa
記憶の壁に 書き込まれた 真実は
The truth is written on the walls of memory
dare ni mo okasenai
誰にも犯せない
No one can violate it
gimon nante nai kono sekai no shikumi wo buchi kowashichimae sono te de
疑問なんてない この世界の仕組みを ぶち壊しちまえ その手で
We have no questions; we just want to break the structure of this world with our hands
furikakaru sadame kirihiraki ima mirai e kakenukero! Get on!
降りかかる運命 切り開き今 未来へ 駆け抜けろ!Get on!
Clear up the fate that befalls me, and then run to the future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Burst on the fire
akumu no you na kumikomareta genjitsu ni
悪夢のような 組み込まれた現実に
Reality has been assembled like a nightmare
yukiba ushinatte funtsumattemo
行き場を失って 糞詰まっても
Even if our destination is lost, and filled with excrement
kizutsuku yuuki itsudemo nakusanai nara
傷つく勇気 いつでも なくさないなら
We will never lose the courage to get hurt
kotae wa kawaranai
答えは変らない!
Our answers will not change
dasannante nai konosekai no mujun wo buchikowashitai soredake
打算なんてない この世界の矛盾を ぶち壊したい それだけ
We have no plans; we just want to break inconsistencies in this world
kurayami wo nukete tozasareta mama no asu wo tokihanate! Get on!
暗闇をぬけて 閉ざされたままの 明日を 解き放て!Get on!
Pass through the darkness, release that closed-off future! Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
hoshikuzu you sa futari kotoba sae ubaware
星屑のようさ 二人 言葉さえ奪われ
The two of us are like stardust; even our words have been stolen
haiiro no sekai kimyou na genjitsu kibou nado koko ni wa arya shinai dakedo
灰色の世界 奇妙な現実 希望などここにはありゃしない だけど…
It's a grey world, a strange reality; there's no hope here, but...
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
dare ni mo makenai michi no chikara de kazemuki wo kaero
誰にも負けない 未知の力で 風向きを変えろ!
With an unknown power second to none, I will change the direction of the wind
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
me no mae no subete ni tachimukai oretachi no jidai he
目の前のすべてに立ち向かい 俺達の時代へ
We will face everything before us in our time
Get on!
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
nikushimi ga ai ga ishi no chikara ga subete wo kaeru
憎しみが 愛が 意思の力が すべてを変える
Hate, love, and the power of will changes everything
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
mune no oku hajike sou na atsui tamashii no sakebi wo
胸のおく 弾けそうな 熱い魂の 叫びを
A scream of my burning soul seems to burst out of my chest
Burst on the fire
on the fire
Feel rock emotion! Burning rock emotion!
Ordo will not be indebted to anyone.
Quon can't die.
I want to go home for now.
If Quon's not coming back anymore, then I'll make a place like the Garden.
I've been given orders to capture you.
Quon, no.
The mourning would be too heavy for you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Don't let him trick you!
Towa no Quon, Chapter five:
Chapter Five 「The Return of the Invincible」
"A Heroic Return"